

# Mirsahib Gafarov

LEADING ACCOUNTANT CHIEF ACCOUNTANT

- apartment 59, house 12,47th block, Sumgait city
- mirsahib.gafarov@gmail.com
- +994555887729
- in inkedin.com/in/mirsahibqafarov-81245983

### PROFILE

Dedicated and detailoriented Credit specialist and Accountant committed to teamwork. focused on continual professional and personal growth, including the improvement of business and economic knowledge. Bachelor's in Finance and Accounting and related certifications and from Financial institutes. **Experienced Financial** manager in all fields of Finance related departments with 10 years of experience.

#### Certificates

- PMS
- Performance Finance
   Academy Tax Legislation
- Fin Consulting Tax Legislation

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### CHIEF ACCOUNTANT

VELIEV LLC (Pimapen Azerbaijan)

Jun 2023 - present

- Cost calculation
- All Tax and statistics reports
- · Salary, final account and business trip calculation
- · Calculation of salary and sick leave and business trip
- · Establishing cost centers and correct distribution of costs

# Financial and Accounting Consultant CHIEF ACCOUNTANT

Hajigabul Poultry Company LLC

Dec 2022 - May 2023

#### LEADING ACCOUNTANT

Garagashli Broiler OJSC

July 2021 - Nov 2022

#### CHIEF ACCOUNTANT

Absheron Sud LLC

Oct 2020 - July 2021

- Calculating the cost of the product, recording the raw materials and materials received, writing electronic invoices,
- · Preparation of financial and tax reports,
- registration of employees in accordance with labor legislation and calculation of wages

#### LEADING ACCOUNTANT

Garagashli Broiler OJSC

Nov 2018 - Oct 2020

- · Preparation of daily and monthly reports,
- · Preparation of EMS report,
- · preparation of VAT report,
- · Salary calculation,
- · Execution of bank payments

#### ACCOUNTANT

Garagashli Broiler OJSC May 2017 - Nov 2018

#### SPECIALIST OF PROBLEM LOANS

Bank of Baku OJSC

Sep 2014 - Feb 2017

- Making regular calls to high-risk customers with high delay days,
- Investigate the reason for the loan delay.
- Meeting with customers who are in arrears and restructuring the overdue loans

#### SKILLS

Accounting
excel for finance
Microsoft Office
Expense Tracking
Flexibility
Budgeting
Time management
Bank transactions
Tax reports
Mikro
1C (7.7 - 8.3)
Logo Tiger 3
Logo Tiger Enterprise

#### LANGUAGES

English Limited Working Proficiency

Russian Limited Working Proficiency

Turksih Professional Working Proficiency

#### INTERESTS

Music Books Cars

Movies Travel Films

# ASSISTANT ON THE RISKS OF PLASTIC CARDS

# Yapi Kredi Bank Azerbaijan CJSC

Oct 2013 - Sep 2014

Analysis of new customers who have applied for a credit

Measuring risk levels and obtaining approval from workplaces,

Determining credit card limits of customers and measuring risk levels.

Calling customers who have applied for a card and responding to their requests

## JUNIOR LOAN OFFICER

## **Turan Bank OJSC**

Jan 2012 - July 2012

Attracting new bank customers,

Analysis of clients applying for new loans and approval of workplaces,

Also, determining the amount of credit for customers applying for a loan,

Providing consumer and business loans to customers

## INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

## **Turan Bank OJSC**

Jun 2010 - Jan 2012

General banking operations, Intern in credit, operation and cashier fields

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

# Azerbaijan State Economic University

Economy of production and service areas

Sep 20 -July 2012